Nuclear Age History and Humanities Center Records UA027
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Martin Sherwin Subject Files, 1985 -- 1993; 1987 -- 1992; UA027.003; 3.6 Linear Feet
  - IEWSS Meeting, Talloires, 1987-10; UA027.003.004.00016 (Box UA027 Shared 2)
    VHS, Maxell brand tape, 120 HighGrade. A surrogate folder, UA027/003-002/00041, exists as a placeholder at the item's original location. For preservation purposes, the tape is stored here in box 4 of the collection.
- Fundraising Files, 1970 -- 1992; 1986 -- 1991; UA027.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence regarding potential grant opportunities and funding received by the NAHHC. Private foundations and corporate sponsors include the MacArthur Foundation and Johnson and Johnson.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically. Originally, folders were filed according to a color coded system. The color codes are indicated in parenthesis after the original folder title. Folders in this series were color coded green (G).
  - [Amelia Peabody Foundation Grant], 1992; UA027.004.003.00015 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - HHCNAS Fundraising Information, 1985 -- 1987; UA027.004.003.00016 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Johnson and Johnson (G), 1989 -- 1990; UA027.004.003.00017 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Kay, Allen (G), 1988; UA027.004.003.00018 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - MacArthur Foundation (G), 1986 -- 1989; UA027.004.003.00019 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [MacArthur Foundation], 1989; UA027.004.003.00020 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Mellon Foundation (G), 1989; UA027.004.003.00021 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Menefee Foundation (Bill Rubey) (G), 1986 -- 1990; UA027.004.003.00022 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Metro Life INS. CO (G), 1990; UA027.004.003.00023 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Ploughshares Fund (G), 1989; UA027.004.003.00024 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Polansky, Robert (G), 1989; UA027.004.003.00025 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Rapport, B. (G), 1991; UA027.004.003.00026 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Reiss, Jeffrey (G), 1992; UA027.004.003.00027 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Rockerfeller Foundation (G), 1991; UA027.004.003.00028 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Rosen, Louis (G), 1992; UA027.004.003.00029 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Sloan Foundation (G), 1990; UA027.004.003.00030 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - SOROS Foundation (G), 1988; UA027.004.003.00031 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Tax Exempt Information (G), 1970; UA027.004.003.00032 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - The Trust For Mutual Understand. (G), 1988; UA027.004.003.00033 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Tufts Development (G), 1987 -- 1991; UA027.004.003.00034 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - United Technologies Int. Corp. (G), 1990 -- 1991; UA027.004.003.00035 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [United Technologies International Corporation], 1990; UA027.004.003.00036 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - W. Alton Jones Foundation (G), 1987; UA027.004.003.00037 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - The World Bank (G), 1989; UA027.004.003.00038 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
- Moscow Trips, 1988 -- 1993; 1989 -- 1993; UA027.005; 2.4 Linear Feet
  This series contains materials about trips to Moscow by Prof. Sherwin and Tufts University students. Materials include correspondence, travel itineraries, maps, newspapers in Russian and English, student program evaluations, and a video of Tufts students visiting Moscow in 1988. Some records contain confidential information and are restricted.
  - March 1988/Moscow Student Trip (Y), UA027.005.003.00039 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
    This file contains confidential information (passport numbers) and should be checked by staff before use by a researcher.
  - March 1989/Moscow Student Trip (Y), UA027.005.003.00040 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - March 1990/Moscow Student Trip (Y), UA027.005.003.00041 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
    This file contains confidential information (passport numbers) and should be checked by the staff before use by a researcher.
  - March 1992 Student Trip (Y), UA027.005.003.00042 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - MJS/Cortese Jan. 1989 USSR Trip (Y), UA027.005.003.00043 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - MJS/Moscow January 1988 (Y), UA027.005.003.00044 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - MJS/Moscow Nov.1988 (Y), UA027.005.003.00045 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - MJS/Moscow October 1988 (Y), UA027.005.003.00046 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Moscow - April '91 (Y), 1991; UA027.005.003.00047 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Moscow, Buttons], 1989 -- 1993; UA027.005.003.00048 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Moscow, Flag], 1989 -- 1993; UA027.005.003.00049 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Moscow, Student Trip Spring 1988, Video Tape], UA027.005.003.00050 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
    This is a surrogate folder. For preservation purposes the VHS is stored seperately in box 4 of this collection.
  - Moscow - Student Trip Spring 1993 (Y), UA027.005.003.00051 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Moscow Travel Memorabilia], 1989 -- 1993; UA027.005.003.00052 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Moscow Travel Memorabilia], 1989 -- 1993; UA027.005.003.00053 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Nickerson April 1989 (Y), UA027.005.003.00054 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Russia Travel/Insurance (Y), 1989 -- 1993; UA027.005.003.00055 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Tufts University Students Visiting Moscow, Spring 1988, UA027.005.004.00017 (Box UA027 Shared 2)
    VHS tape. A surrogate folder, UA027/005-003/00051, exists as a placeholder at the item's original location. For preservation purposes, the tape is stored here in box 4 of the collection.
- Daily Logs, 1989 -- 1992; UA027.006; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains daily logs, telephone messages, and faxes addressed to Prof. Martin Sherwin.
  Folders are arranged chronologically.
  - [Telephone Messages], UA027.006.003.00056 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Telephone Messages, 1989-1990], UA027.006.003.00057 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Daily Logs - August 1990, UA027.006.003.00058 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Daily Logs - September 1990, UA027.006.003.00059 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Daily Logs - October 1990, UA027.006.003.00060 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Daily Logs - November 1990, UA027.006.003.00061 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - Daily Logs - December 1990, UA027.006.003.00062 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Daily Logs] August/September 1991, UA027.006.003.00063 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Daily Logs] October 1991, UA027.006.003.00064 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
  - [Daily Logs] January 1992, UA027.006.003.00065 (Box UA027 Shared 3)
- Additional accessions, UA027.007
  - NAHHC, daily logs, UA027-001 (Box data_value_missing_eb60e42e28531e5a628c9d5df8c1b9a5, Box 1)